<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tinappay</string>

<string name="monay1">
•	4 cups all-purpose flour\n
•	1 1/2 teaspoon salt\n
•	1/2 cup powdered milk\n
•	1 packet active dry yeast\n
•	1 1/2 cup plus 2 tablespoons warm water\n
•	1/2 cup sugar\n
•	2 tablespoons unsalted butter, melted\n
•	3 egg yolks\n
    </string>

<string name="monay2">
1.	In a bowl, mix the flour, salt, and powdered milk together. Set aside.\n\n
2.  Meanwhile, in another bowl mix the yeast with 1 ½ cups of the warm water. Make sure that the yeast is active, meaning bubbles should be visible. Add the sugar and give it a stir. In a small bowl, mix the melted butter with 2 egg yolks. Now, mix both the yeast mixture and the butter mixture together.\n\n
3.  Slowly mix the wet and dry ingredients together until it becomes a dough. Knead the dough and form a ball. Put the dough in a bowl and cover it with a kitchen cloth. Leave it for 2 hours until the dough doubles its size. (An alternative is put the dough in a 180-degree oven for 30-40 minutes.)\n\n
4.  Preheat the oven to 375 degrees.\n\n
5.  Knead the dough again for about 5 minutes. Form a log and slice it into the desired size. Coat a baking sheet with cooking spray or vegetable oil and arrange the rolls on the pan. Beat the remaining yolk and water together in a bowl to form an egg wash. Brush the egg wash on top of the rolls. Bake until the tops turn golden brown, about 20 minutes.\n\n
</string>


<string name="pandesal1">
•	2 1/4 teaspoon active dry yeast\n
•	1 1/4 cup (285 g) whole milk, warmed to 100-105 degrees F\n
•	3 cups (390 g) all-purpose flour\n
•	1 1/2 cups (195 g) bread flour\n
•	1 1/2 teaspoon kosher salt (Diamond Crystal kosher salt)\n
•	3 Tablespoons (43 g) unsalted butter, room temperature\n
•	1/3 cup (70 g) granulated sugar\n
•	2 large eggs, lightly whisked\n
•	2 breadcrumbs, as needed\n
    </string>

<string name="pandesal2">
1.  Dissolve yeast in warm milk. Add 2 teaspoons of sugar. Stir to combine. Let stand for 5-10 minutes until yeast has activated and mixture is foamy.\n\n
2.  In a large bowl, whisk together all-purpose flour, bread flour, and salt. Set aside.\n\n
3.  Pour yeast mixture into the bowl of a stand mixer fitted with a hook attachment. Add remaining sugar, butter, and lightly whisked eggs.\n\n
4.  With the mixer running on low speed, add the flour mixture in three additions. Once all the flour has been added, increase speed to medium. Continue to knead until dough comes together to form a smooth ball.\n\n
5.  Remove from mixing bowl and transfer to a lightly oiled bowl. Cover with plastic wrap and let dough rise at room temperature for 1 hour, until dough has doubled in volume*. Punch dough down and divide into 24 equal parts.\n\n
6.  Roll dough into balls and dip the top of the bread roll into breadcrumbs. Place rolls breadcrumb side up on a parchment lined 18x13-inch baking sheet. Cover dough with plastic wrap to prevent from drying out. Allow bread rolls to rise for 20-30 minutes, until bread rolls have puffed up.\n\n
7.  Preheat oven to 350 degrees F. Remove plastic wrap and bake for 20-25 minutes until fragrant and golden brown. Eat bread rolls warm or at room temperature.\n\n
</string>

<string name="cheesedog1">
•	12 slices white bread\n
•	3 hot dogs, cut into 4 strips\n
•	4 ounces quick melt cheese, cut into 24 thin strips\n
•	2 eggs\n
•	¼ cup milk\n
•	1 cup Panko bread crumbs\n
•	canola oil\n
    </string>

<string name="cheesedog2">
1.  rim edges of each bread and with a rolling pin, flatten until very thin. \n\n
2.  Arrange a piece of hotdog and two cheese strips at the edge of the bread facing you and roll bread into a log to enclose filling. Press lightly on seams to completely seal (or secure with toothpicks and remove when ready to dredge in bread crumbs). Repeat with remaining bread slices.\n\n
3.  In a bowl, combine eggs and milk and whisk together until well-beaten.\n\n
4.  In a shallow dish, place Panko bread crumbs.\n\n
5.  Dip the bread roll in egg mixture and roll in bread crumbs, patting down crumbs to fully coat. Repeat with the remaining rolls.\n\n
6.  Arrange breaded rolls in a single layer on a baking sheet and freeze for 3 to 5 minutes.\n\n
7.  In a wide, thick-bottomed pan over medium heat, heat about 2-inches deep of oil. Place prepared bread rolls seam side down and deep-fry, turning as needed, until golden and crunchy.\n\n
8.  Remove from pan and drain on a wire rack set over a baking sheet. Serve hot with catsup for dipping.\n\n
    </string>

<string name="startbread1">
•	3 cups bread flour\n
•	1 cup cake flour\n
•	¾ cup sugar\n
•	2 tsp instant yeast\n
•	1 tsp salt\n
•	¼ cup margarine\n
•	¾ cup warm water\n
•	¾ cup warm water\n
•	1 egg for eggwash\n
•	sugar for topping\n
    </string>

<string name="qwe">
1.  In a bowl. Mix bread flour, cake flour, sugar, powdered milk, and instant yeast.\n\n
2.  Make a well at the center of the mixture and add margarine, salt, and warm water. Using a spatula or wooden spoon, mix well until incorporated and turns into a dough.\n\n
3.  Transfer the dough on a work table and floured surface. Knead for at about 10 minutes until dough texture becomes smooth and elastic. Shape it into a big round ball. Then transfer in an oiled bowl and cover with plastic wrap or a damp cloth. Set aside in an unused oven or warm place for about an hour.\n\n
4.  Punch the dough in the middle after an hour to release air. With your weighing scale, take a portion of dough and measure 60 grams and roll into a ball. Repeat the process until all dough is weighed and rolled into small buns.\n\n
5.  To make the star breads signature crack on top. Make an X or star slice on top of the dough using a scissor or sharp knife.\n\n
6.  Transfer the dough into a baking tray lined with baking paper. Cover the dough with a damp cloth for 10 – 15 minutes and let it rest for a moment. To prevent it from being fluffy, avoid letting them rest too long. Pre-heat oven at 200°C.\n\n
7.  Before baking, brush it on top with egg wash and sprinkle sugar on top. Bake the bread for about 20 – 25 minutes or until the top is light brown. Remove from oven and let it cool.\n\n
8.  8.Remove from oven and let it cool. Serve and Enjoy. Bon Appetit!\n\n
</string>




<string name="spanish1">
•	1 and 1/4 cups warm milk 105-115 F\n
•	2 and 1/4 tsp active dry yeast\n
•	4 and 1/2 cup all-purpose flour, divided + up to 1/8 cup extra for kneading\n
•	1 tsp salt\n
•	1/2 cup sugar\n
•	1/3 cup canola oil\n
•	2 large eggs lightly beaten\n
•	2 large eggs lightly beaten\n
•	1/4 cup evaporated milk\n
•	For the Spanish Bread Filling\n
•	1/4 cup all-purpose flour\n
•	1/2 cup` bread crumbs\n
•	1/3 cup butter\n
•	2/3 cup brown sugar\n
•	1/3 cup evaporated milk\n


</string>

<string name="spanish2">
Make the Bread Dough\n\n
1.  In a mixing bowl, combine milk and yeast. Let stand for 5 minutes or until foamy. Add the eggs, sugar, oil and salt. Stir everything with a wooden spoon. Add 4 cups of flour, one cup at a time while stirring. The mixture will turn into a shaggy dough.\n\n
2.  Sprinkle just enough of the remaining 1/2 cup of flour and keep stirring until the dough gathers in the center. Turn the dough over on a floured board and knead it until it is smooth and elastic, about 6-10 minutes. As you knead, dust your hands and your board as needed to help with the stickiness. You may need to use up to 1/8 cup of additional flour.\n\n
3.  Shape the dough into a ball and place it a bowl. Cover and let rise for 1 and 1/2 hours, or until the size is doubled. You can make the filling at this point.\n\n
4.  Gently punch the dough down and divide it into 18-20 portions. Using a small rolling pin or your hands, flatten each portion into an oval that is about the size of your hands. Spread about a tablespoon of the filling across the surface of the dough and roll it into a log. Repeat with all the other portions. Arrange the rolls in a large baking tray that is greased or lined with parchment paper. Brush evaporated milk on each of the rolls and dip them in breadcrumbs. Cover them loosely with plastic wrap and let them rise for an hour.\n\n
5.  Preheat the oven to 350 F. Bake the Spanish bread for 15-20 minutes, or until the rolls are lightly golden.\n\n
Spanish Bread Filling\n\n
Heat the butter in a small saucepan until it is bubbly. Add the flour and the breadcrumbs and stir the mixture vigorously with a wire whisk for a few seconds. This is a grainy mixture at this point. Immediately add the milk and keep stirring until the mixture loosens up a bit. Stir for 30 seconds more and turn off heat. Stir in the sugar well until it is incorporated. Set aside to cool. This mixture is a chunky paste.\n\n
</string>

</resources>